Friends, I welcome you to Maharajganj gate from 19th,
through my channel Vastu Anurup, I will tell you that
during this time the
name is
Veeravratam, as I told you
in the previous video, now to make my channel you
must subscribe, then I will tell you that if you enter the
name of the company, then
open it,
after clicking on the master, see
here the reader is looking, employment
registration is coming, in this way the company has
hit, then I have the name of the insurance company,
so here I have Insurance Company Ltd,
after clicking on Insurance Company,
new is coming here, so I have appointed here,
subscribe here,
I have entered the name of the insurance company,
subscribe to the channel here,
I have entered the mobile number of the company here, then
I will appoint here,
this is the Registrar appointed, appointed, the
festival of GST, GST number is coming,
oath taken here, in this
I have to select the service here,
till there
is two in it, after collecting the service, the
question credit is coming here,
nothing is getting created here, you have to
leave a message from this, after that you have to enter
here  But Aghamsarshan,
click here and
appoint me, so I will subscribe to appoint me here, the
district bar of Jhaal is in the tehsil Bhadra, the
city Mukul Dwivedi, Dr.
Jhaal,
he is making an address line here, in this, there is
no need to make any ad type or Jhaal's Idea lights, it is
asking for the pin code below, I will put the pin code here,
then
I should
put the pin code, it is asking for the distance,
how far is it from there, so I will put the
distance here, it is making a fool from below, I will
shift it,
after doing this app, it has come here, it is very important to put a
pick mark here in the film type
and we use it here, if there is an
email address here below, then
we will put it here and
after that click here and subscribe,
subscribe to the insurance company in Mera Insurance Company,
that Yuvraj subscribe to that,
after clicking on the slipper number, the job is done,
now we click on click oil here and
subscribe because subscribe to this channel
and
subscribe to this channel, if you liked the video, then
please do subscribe to my video
and subscribe to my channel
Thank you
[music]
what happened